MUHAMMAD FAIQ MUBAROK

faigmubarok@gmail.com | +62 821 1774 8606 | Purwokerto Selatan, Banyumas

SUMMARY

As an active fourth-semester Information Systems student at Telkom University Institute of Technology Purwokerto, I possess skills in front-end website development. Experienced in utilizing HTML, CSS, and JavaScript technologies to develop responsive and user-friendly web interfaces. My interest lies in working as a proficient front-end developer, contributing to innovative projects, and continuously enhancing skills in the latest web technologies.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

UKost Feb 2024 - Present

- Developing an information system for centralized boarding and renting reservations and rentals in Purwokerto.
- Analyzing system designs and implementing user interfaces for client and admin side.

Roadwave, Final Project for Web Design and Programming Course

Des 2023 - Jan 2024

- Collaborate within a team to complete the final project in the course, which involves creating a website for an online clothing business known as Roadwave Apparel.
- Formulate the concept for the website to be developed, along with the planned web usage flow.
- My focus is on creating a responsive and user-friendly interface on the client side.

Personal Website Feb 2024 - Mar 2024

- Designed and developed a personal portfolio website using HTML, Tailwind, Flowbite and JavaScript. This website is designed to display my portfolio, skills and contact information in detail.
- Create a personal portfolio website from start to finish, starting with designing the user interface using Figma to illustrate ideas, continuing with the implementation of a responsive design, as well as enhancing with animation and interactivity using JavaScript.

EDUCATION

Institut Teknologi Telkom Purwokerto

Sept 2022 - Present

Undergraduate of Information Systems

MA Husnul Khotimah

Jul 2019 - Mei 2022

Mathematics and Natural Science

TECHNICAL SKILLS

React JS (Beginner) CSS (Intermediate)

Javascript (Intermediate) HTML 5 (Intermediate)

Tailwind CSS (Intermediate) Git (Intermediate)

Github (Intermediate)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Soft Skill: Communication, Leadership, Creativity, Problem Solve, Team Work.
- Activities: Dies Natalis SI 7 (PIC), Information System Student Organization (HRD).